{
    "subject": "Donald_Knuth",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "TeX",
    "human_readable": "Donald Knuth created TeX.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7595142126083374,
            "question": "Who created TeX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.571922242641449,
            "question": "Why was TeX created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3324742019176483,
            "question": "What is TeX known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28862354159355164,
            "question": "What are some uses of TeX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22816811501979828,
            "question": "What are the main features of TeX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13155244290828705,
            "question": "Is there a specific field where TeX is commonly used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1058012843132019,
            "question": "What kind of software is TeX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09020061045885086,
            "question": "How has TeX impacted typesetting and publishing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07291516661643982,
            "question": "Are there any alternative typesetting systems besides TeX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06767671555280685,
            "question": "What programming language is TeX typically written in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Donald Knuth created TeX.",
            "html": "yago_19692_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any alternative typesetting systems besides TeX?",
            "html": "yago_19692_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has TeX impacted typesetting and publishing?",
            "html": "yago_19692_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of software is TeX?",
            "html": "yago_19692_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19692_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\n\"Donald Knuth created TeX.\"\n\nHere's the JSON response:\n\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Donald Knuth developed the first version of TeX in 1978 to deal with revisions to his series \u201cthe Art of Computer Programming\u201d. This information supports the query \"Donald Knuth created TeX.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}